

Ana Nenadic

Front end web developer

Storgatan 102B, 171 55 Solna, Sweden I +46 72 256 4083 I ana.nenadic18@gmail.com

Portfolio: https://bela90.github.io/ Linkedin profile: https://www.linkedin.com/in/ana-nenadic-b3860476/

About Me	
A highly motivated, enthusiastic and creative web developer with experience in bringing design and functionality of the web page to life from the scratch. Passionate about front end performance and adaptive/responsive web design.	
Language	
Croatian En	glish Swedish
Skills	
HTML	
CSS	
Java Script	
jQuery	
Bootstrap	
Responsive	
design	
UX/UI design	
Sketch	
PHP/ mySql	
Git/ Bitbucket	
Hobbies	

Education

Bachelor of Business Informatics

University of Zagreb, Faculty of Organization and Informatics 2010 - 2014

Front end web developer nanodegree program

Udacity

2017 - 2018

Web development and coding specialization

Coursera, University of Michigan 2016

Experience

Front end web developer

One planet rating, Stockholm 2017 - Present

Developing and designing new features from sketching to coding. Redesigning old features according to stakeholders/ customer requests, adding responsiveness to the mobile and tablet version of the site, complete redesigning of the mobile version browser, coordinating with backend and marketing team.

Summer camp FOI internship

University of Zagreb

July 2013 - August 2013

Developing faculty library application, from idea to the final product. Working tools and programs: HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, PHP, mySQL